In love and life there's only one way to go.
Going All the Way is a drama, romance film directed by Mark Pellington.
Korean War--era veterans and ex-classmates "Gunner" Casselman
and "Sonny" Burns reunite upon their return home.
Gunner, who spent the war years abroad, is trying to convince his mother that his gal Marty is good enough for
him, while Sonny, who was stationed stateside, is torn between loyal Buddy and tempting Gale Ann.
As they commiserate, the men realize that they're
outgrowing the lives they lived before the war.
Williard 'Sonny' Burns, played by Jeremy Davies.
Tom 'Gunner' Casselman, played by Ben Affleck.
Buddy Porter, played by Amy Locane.
Marty Pilcher, played by Rachel Weisz.
Alma Burns, played by Jill Clayburgh.
Gale Ann Thayer, played by Rose McGowan.
Going All the Way is a 1997 American comedy-drama film directed by
Mark Pellington, in his feature film directorial debut.
The film was written by Dan Wakefield, based on his 1970 novel and stars Jeremy
Davies, Ben Affleck, Amy Locane, Rachel Weisz and Rose McGowan.
The film explores themes of friendship, based on novel or book,
marriage, korean war (1950-53), indianapolis.
The tone is emotional.